A Guide to the Rodman C. Rockefeller papers FA1350
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Educational Interests, 1956-2001; V; 4.74 Cubic Feet 10 letter document boxes and 2 legal document boxes
  - Institute of International Education - Budget Proposal, 1998 May 12 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Institute of International Education - 1998 Budget (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Institute of International Education, Development Committee Correspondence, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Institute of International Education - Development Committee Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Institute of International Education - Development Committee Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Institute of International Education - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Institute of International Education - Correspondence, 1999 January-June (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Institute of Internationa Education - Correspondence, 1999 January-June (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Institute of International Education - Correspondence, 1999 July-December (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Institute of International Education - Correspondence, 2000 January-June (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Institute of International Education - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Institute of International Education - 1997 Annual Report (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Institute of International Education - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1996-2000 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Institute of International Education - Executive Board of Committee Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Institute of International Education - Nominating Committee Minutes, 1999 January 7 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Institute of International Education - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Institute of International Education - Fulbright Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Institute of International Education - Fulbright Annual Report, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Institute of International Education - Fulbright Annual Report, 1997 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Institute of International Education - Academy of Educational Development, 1996 July 17 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Institute of International Education - "For the Visit of Mr. Rodman Rockefeller, Dr. Eduardo Andere and Mr. Donald Hamilton to the Institute of International Education", Report, 1996 September 24 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Institute of International Education - Fulbright Commission Background - Report and Accounts, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Institute of International Education - Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - The Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for Social Sciences - Dartmouth College, 1983 September 23-25 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - The American School Foundation, 1987-1989 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Brooks School Endowment, 1981-1987 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Brooks School Yearbook Subscription, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Columbia University, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Deerfield Academy - Correspondence, 1984-1997 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Harvard University - David Rockefeller Center for Latin American Studies Directory, 1997-1998 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Morehouse College, 1997 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - The New School - Board Member Listings, 1984-1987 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - The New School - Commission on Continuing Education, 1983 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - The New School Correspondence, 1979-1984 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - The New School Correspondence, 1985-1997 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - The New School - History of the School, by Nathan W. Levin, 1982 September (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - The New School - Real Estate, 1985 September-October (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Gifts to The New School, 1971-1987 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - New York University - Center for Philanthropy - Advisory Board, 1998-1999 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - New York University - Naomi Levine, New York Alliance for the Public Schools, 1988-2000 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - New York College of Osteopathic Medicine, 1986-1987 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Purchase College, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Zamorano School - Correspondence, 1984-1997 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Zamorano School and The Interracial Council for Business Opportunity - Miscellaneous Pamphlets, Articles and Booklets (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Phillips Exeter Academy - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Harvard Business School - Booker and International Basic Economy Corporation, Case Study, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Harvard Business School - Booker and International Basic Economy Corporation, Case Study, 1980 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Harvard Business School (IBEC) World Food Policy Seminar, 1979 May 13-14 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Harvard Business School - General Correspondence, 1967; 1979-1986 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Dartmouth General Correspondence, 1990-1999 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Dartmouth General Correspondence, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Dartmouth General Correspondence, 1976-1989 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Dartmouth Hood Museum, 1984-1999 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Dartmouth 30th Reunion Dinner, 1984 May 12 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Dartmouth 35th Reunion, 1989 June 12 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Dartmouth 40th Reunion, 1994 May (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Dartmouth 45th Reunion - Hanover, NH, 1999 June 14-17 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Dartmouth, Nelson A. Rockefeller Center - Advisory Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Dartmouth, Nelson A. Rockefeller Center - Annual Reports, 1992-1998 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1983 June 30 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, 1983 September 23 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, 1984 February 23-24 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, Hanover, New Hampshire, 1984 October 26-27 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, 1985 May 18 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, Hanover, New Hampshire, 1985 October 25-26 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, Lebanon, New Hampshire, 1986 October 24-25 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, Hanover, New Hampshire, 1987 May 15-16 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, Hanover, New Hampshire, 1987 October 23-24 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, 1988 May 6-7 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, 1988 September 16-17 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, Hanover, New Hampshire, 1989 May 19-20 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, Hanover, New Hampshire, 1989 September 17 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, Hanover, New Hampshire, 1989 September 29-30 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, Lebanon, New Hampshire, 1990 April 6-7 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, 1990 September 21-22 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, 1991 January 25-26 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, 1991 May 3-4 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, 1991 November 1-2 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, 1992 May 29-30 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, 1992 October 23-24 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, 1993 January 14-15 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, 1993 January 22-23 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, 1993 May 1 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meeting, 1993 July 8-9 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Board of Visitors Meetings, 1993 October 16 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - The Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for the Social Sciences Board of Visitors Meeting, Agenda, January 14 -15, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Challenge Grant, 1997-1999 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Challenge Grant, 1997-1999 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1993 January-June (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1993 July-December (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1996-2000 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1996-2000 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Correspondence, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Dedication Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Dedication Correspondence, 1983 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Dedication - Transcripts, Articles and Pamphlets, 1983 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center - George Demko, 1989-1991 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Dinner, 1999 April 21 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center - Director's Search, 1982; 1985 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - The Governor's Symposium, Dartmouth, 1993 April 29-30 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center - Mission and Governance Documents, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center - Miscellaneous Pamphlets (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller - Dartmouth Pledges, 1983-1990 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller - Dartmouth Pledges, 1983-1990 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Dartmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center Proposals (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Memorial Garden - Possible Contributors, 1981 March-May (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Frank Smallwood Dinner, 1986 May 9 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Dartmouth - Tuck School - Board of Overseers, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Dartmouth - Tuck School - Board of Overseers, 1980-1981 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Dartmouth - Tuck School - Board of Overseers, 1982 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Dartmouth - Tuck School - Board of Overseers, 1983 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Dartmouth - Tuck School - Correspondence, 1975-1983 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Dartmouth - Tuck School - Correspondence (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - College Park at Princeton Forrestal Center - Supplementary Material (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Harvard University - Directory of Faculty, Fellows and Professional Staff, 1999-2001 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Metro International - Fulbright Awards Dinner, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Institute for International Education, Correspondence, 1999 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Institute for International Education, Correspondence, 1999 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Remarks - Fulbright International Center, Washington D.C., 1998 May 28 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Future of Fulbright Exchange Program and Acceptance Speech for Fulbright Award, United Nations, 1998 May 18 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - The Future of the Fulbright Exchange Program by Rodman C. Rockefeller (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Dartmouth NAR Center - 10th Anniversary, Hanover, NH, 1993 October 16 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - The International Forum - Wharton School, Philadelphia, PA, 1991 September 6 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - American School Fundraising Kick -Off - University Club, NY, 1989 February 20 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Reflections on 25 Years - Darmouth, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University Master of Science, 1956-1958 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Harvard Business School Award (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - American School Foundation Photographs, 1988-1989 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Institute of International Education Photographs, 1994-1997 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Deerfield Academy - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Darmouth - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center - Contributions, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Darmouth 30th Reunion, 1984 June 11-13 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Kenneth Durr Research Materials, VI; 4.56 Cubic Feet 12 letter document boxes
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Subject Files (Box 84, Folder 1-14)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Subject Files (Box 85, Folder 1-18)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Subject Files (Box 86, Folder 1-13)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Subject Files (Box 87, Folder 1-16)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Subject Files (Box 88, Folder 1-12)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Subject Files (Box 89, Folder 1-6)
  - Interviews (Box 89, Folder 7-27)
  - Booker Correspondence (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1968-1986 (Box 90, Folder 2-12)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller - Nelson A. Rockefeller 1950's Correspondence (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Annual Reports, 1947-1973 (Box 91, Folder 2-28)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Annual Reports, 1974-1984 (Box 92, Folder 1-11)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Annual Reports, 1963-1977 (Box 93, Folder 1-2)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - History (Box 93, Folder 3-8)
  - Oral History Project (Box 94, Folder 1-6)
    Restricted - In accordance with terms of release
  - Oral History Project (Box 95, Folder 1-4)